One Pace Premium
Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
It's not like we've seen
the end of the world with our own eyes.
That's why we gotta cast off - together, we can!
Sailing from sea to sea,
saying it's nothing but a fairy tale.
Truth is stranger than fiction, isn't it?
Don't pretend you can't see it.
Common sense is only what the majority says it is!
It's not like we've seen
the end of the world with our own eyes.
So let's go, Captain I'll-Do-It-My-Way!
Whaddya mean, "no can do"?
We haven't even started yet!
I wanna know it all! Now, yes, we can!
Yes, we can! You can! This moment...
We can! I can! With this feeling of freedom...
Now... Now, oh yes, we can!
Yes, we can!
At Rightflank Fortress
Here comes a Rain-Ruption!
What?!
A big splash of water?!
It'll cause floods!
Get to high ground!
Run!
But...
It's too late!
Meanwhile, Kin'emon and Kanjuro are
climbing the elephant's left leg...
Finally, it stopped.
What was the shaking all about?
I don't know.
But we're coming to the crucial point.
Hold on, cat! Nekozaemon!
Now hurry up!
The sun is setting, Nekozaemon!
Isn't it too much for a cat to climb this elephant?
Kanjuro!
No, it's not.
Cats are good tree climbers.
They are!
Water?!
What?!
Oh, that's water overflowing from a Rain-Ruption that poured over the country...
Water is no good! It will melt Nekozaemon!
There is no time to lose...
But again, halfway to the top, we...
The Whale Forest - Luffy's Group
Oh, that was a hell of a rain!
Rain-Ruptions aren't actually a type of rain.
Huh?
Twice a day, Zunesha sprays water on itself.
So that was a blast of seawater.
The water passes through a filtration system at the center of the city to aqueducts
and becomes the drinking water for the whole nation.
Fish fall along with the seawater, so we never run out of food.
Rain-Ruptions provide us with a lot.
Hey, Straw Hat!
Oh, the bear!
I can't leave this forest, so can you tell our captain about us and bring him here?!
Oh, you can't?
Okay!
I'm counting on you!
Bepo was born here, but since he's a pirate,
he's now under the care of Master Nekomamushi, the boss of the forest.
Kurau City - Zoro and the others
It's flooding!
There's a shark! A shark?! Why?!
You went way too high!
This is high enough.
Seawater?
Maybe, that was the giant elephant spraying water on itself.
It seems like both the town and the forest are adapted to this water level.
Well, seeing the water amount...
I guess you're right!
That means this happens every day...
I wouldn't want that tremendous downpour every day!
We must find everybody quickly and get off of this annoying island!
Hey, there's Luffy!
At the edge of the town!
He's with the Nami-dog girl and the jump rabbit from before!
He's being fooled and is being taken to their lair...
What is it, Usopp?!
Luffy's been bitten!
What?! So they're really...
The water will drain away soon.
I know he's here!
I told you he's not!
Bring him here
or this country will be destroyed!
I don't know what you're talking about!
I really don't know!
What else can I say?!
Who was it?
You told me the name of the guy who attacked this country before.
His name is Jack.
I saw his obituary in the newspaper a few days ago.
It said, after he overran this country,
he attacked four Navy ships that were transporting Doflamingo
and sank two of them but they struck back.
What?! Was he there at Dressrosa?!
He attacked the ships with the Navy admiral and the former fleet admiral on board.
He must have a screw loose.
It said his death wasn't confirmed.
I think he's still alive.
We'll never forgive Jack!
It's really foggy.
Will Zoro and the others be there too?
I think so.
I gave them directions to our hidden fortress.
Chambres
Oh, it's you guys!
Hey, Luffy! Where were you bitten?!
Do you still have your limbs?
Hey, you Nami-dog girl right there!
He's our captain!
You wanna eat him, don't you?!
I won't let you do that, you predatory tramp!
If you don't give us back him and our friends who came here first,
you'll see these three swords fire up!
I can't believe it.
I think you have the wrong idea.
But that's okay. We're here now.
What?
Look over there in the fog carefully...
There are guards and a gate to the fortress.
Wanda! Who are they-gara?
Are they the ones who invaded the Whale Forest?!
They didn't mean any harm!
The Welcoming Bell didn't ring by mistake
and one of them got lost in the Whale Forest!
Open the gate and let everybody know!
That the Straw Hats are here!
What?! Is that who they-gara are?!
Inside the fortress
Nami!
Nami!!
Luffy and the others are here!
They're finally here!
Nami! Luffy and the others arrived!
They made it safely!
They did?! Really, Chopper?!
They're at the fortress gate!
Oh, your friends are here. That's good.
Nami!
I'm sorry.
They're important guests!
Prepare to welcome our great saviors' friends!
Garchu!
Welcome, Straw Hats!
Welcome!
What?! What?!
Oh?! What the...?!
The atmosphere's quite upbeat!
This isn't what we heard about!
Garchu!
What's "Garchu"?
I thought the people of your race hate humans.
Race, huh?
That's probably what those who don't know other Minks think and get scared of.
Other Minks?
To us, you-teia guys are just Monkey Minks who have less hair.
You're the same Mink Tribe, just a different type.
Oh, so we humans are Monkey Minks.
That's right.
We judge someone by their character, not by their race.
Garchu!
We take pride in the hair covering our bodies, but,
you-teia guys have those beautiful...
..."lesser mink coats"
and quite a lot of us admire it.
Oh, you're right!
Oh, look! That's Nami and Chopper!
I'm glad that they're okay!
Nami!
Nami! I'm happy for you! Garchu!
Garchu!
I got caught! Let me through!
Alright! Garchu! Garchu!
That's great! Garchu!
They're very friendly!
That's so different from what I expected!
Luffy!
Everybody!
Oh, you guys!
I'm so happy to see you again!
Nami! Chopper!
Usopp!
Sorry to keep you waiting, Chopper!
So Sanji, Brook, and Momo are all fine too!
I'm sorry!
Sanji-kun is...
Oh, the sun is setting!
We can't go any farther today!
Mm-hm! Let's go back to the ship
and climb again tomorrow!
I like how you drink!
Here, have another cup!
Go ahead and drink!
It's our special "Monkey Wine."
It's made from the abundance of fruits in the forest.
Yeah! It tastes good!
Go away, you fools!
Don't press yourselves against me!
What?! Let's play!
Let me give you love bites!
Let us garchu!
Let me lick you!
Shut up! Don't be such a baby!
Whoa-whoa, don't get mad, Zoro!
Look how well they're treating us!
You're so rude!
Please overlook these cultural differences.
Minkship is a friendly gesture to us.
It's delicious! What kind of meat is this?!
That's hippo.
And these are lizard, alligator, and frog.
We don't eat animals with fur.
But why do you welcome us like this?
Because you-teia guys are our saviors' friends!
Saviors... What happened exactly?
N-Nooooo!!
Brook!
What a relief! I read in the newspaper!
I'm glad that you're all okay!
Luffy-san!
What happened to you?!
I'm sorry about Sanji-san!
I'm too ashamed to face you!
But I don't have a facial surface anyway.
Oh?! Hey, aren't you with Momo?!
Yes, of course, he's okay but it seems like...
...he doesn't really like the Minks.
What? Doesn't he like these nice people?
No. He shuts himself in a room and never comes out.
But that's good for us.
Huh?
Luffy-san, could I have a word with you?
Come this way.
All of you newcomers to Zou, come here!
Where is Kin'emon-san now?
He should be arriving soon.
I see. That's perfect.
I want you to try not to use words like
"samurai" or "Wano Country" in this country.
Don't use them if you can.
If you use those words, you might offend many people
and anger them or make them hate you.
Offend?
Anger? Hate?
Why "samurai"...
Well, this country was actually...
I found you!
Baron Corpse!
Here they come!
"Corpse"?!
You'll reach the Rightflank Forest! And you'll find the corpse of your-teia friend there!
C-Corpse?!
So the corpse of a friend...
She was talking about Brook!
We call him so with affection.
That's very confusing.
To be honest, I was surprised...
I didn't know there was such a tempting race in this world!
Stop it! Help!
We Dog Minks... h-have a thing for bones!
Stop chewing on me!
How stupid...
By the way, Luffy, what happened to Tra-guy?
Oh, he went to the Bear Forest.
Hey! More importantly, what should we do about Sanji-kun?!
Like I said before, he left a note.
So don't you think it's gonna be alright?
Yeah, it's not like he was kidnapped.
I'm worried because it didn't look right!
I'm sorry!
We couldn't do anything!
You don't need to cry!
Well, you know what, guys?
Frankly, we're just confused right now.
We only have a rough idea of what's going on.
He's right!
The last time we talked, you guys said you were facing Big Mom's ship!
Now we finally got to Zou and there are those talking animals on the elephant's back and the city's ruined!
We thought the Mink Tribe was our enemy,
but instead, they welcomed us so warmly!
They even told us we're their saviors' friends!
Could you tell us everything in detail, Nami?
What's happened to your group since you left Dressrosa eleven days ago?
Yeah, I guess I was a little upset.
Okay, I'll tell you
everything as it happened.
What we encountered that day off the coast of Dressrosa was...
...the Big Mom Pirates' enormous singing ship!
Singing?!
Ship! Ship!
Their combatants that we could identify were the duo that Luffy met on the Fishman Island.
Mama! I see Caesar! Grr!
Let's sink their ship and recover just Caesar-soir!
And another one...
He's one of the Worst Generation.
Capone "Gang" Bege!
Bege?
Seems like they became Big Mom's subordinates.
They came for Caesar,
but he was more scared of them.
But, frankly speaking, we had no chance to get away from them.
And we knew they'd take us down if nothing was done!
Let's get out of here with Coup de Burst!
What about Gaon Cannon?!
No! We don't have enough Cola!
I have another idea instead!
If you have an idea, just do it!
Help us if you wanna survive!
Brook! Let's fight them at the stern
and let them drop their guard!
Soul Parade!
Cho-Cho-Cho-Cho-Cho... Chopperemon?!
Catch, Chopper!
No! Let go of me!
I'll get even with you bastard!
How could you use my body like a bag?!
We won't help you
if you don't stop resisting!
No!
All yours, Sanji!
That's Caesar! Grr!
What are they doing-bon?!
Nice pitch, Chopper!
How can he fly?!
Poele a Frire...
Frying Pan
...Spectre!
Spectrum
Oh no! Grr!
Turn away-bon!
Ship!
The starboard side's been damaged!
Okay! It's my turn!
Clima-Tact
Weather...
...Egg!
Come hatch, rain clouds!
Rain Tempo!
Why did the weather change in just that area-bon?!
We're gonna lose them! Grr!
Only you guys could do that!
That doesn't make me blush, you idiot!
That was a white-knuckler!
That's super!
That's great!
Stop it!
Well, it was a big deal I guess but...
And how many days did it take to get to Zou from there?
We arrived here the next day.
Seems like Zou was nearby at that time.
That was 10 days ago.
As far as I could see,
the oldest sign of destruction
in the city at the center of Zou was...
...from a little more than two weeks ago.
That's right.
And by 10 days ago,
most of the country had been destroyed.
But on that day, Nami and the others arrived here.
That can only be described as a miracle!
If not for their courage
and Chopper's medical expertise,
every single person in the Mokomo Dukedom would've been helplessly killed...
I know that it just happened and it still hurts,
so if you don't want to talk about it, that's fine but...
No, I'll tell you everything.
You-teia people have the right to know everything.
Hey!
Everybody!
Duke-sama has woken up!
That's great!
Duke-sama... He's all right now...
Okay! Let's go examine his condition now!
Miyagi! Tristan!
Oh, wait for me!
Okay, okay!
Let me go at it and learn from you!
Dr. Miyagi! You're hopping too much!
Wanda!
Duke Inuarashi said he'd like to see the saviors!
Okay, I'll be right up!
You-teia guys, will you come with me?!
Yeah but who's Inuarashi?
He's the duke of the Mokomo Dukedom.
Which means he's the ruler of the country!
He'd been in a coma ever since the city was wiped out.
So has the other one.
The other one?!
Yes! This country has two rulers!
"King of the Day" - Duke Inuarashi!
"King of the Night" - Master Nekomamushi!
Captain!
You came for us!
Captain, it's amazing that you beat Doflamingo!
No, that's Straw Hat-ya's...
We have a lot to catch up on!
Let's go deeper into the forest!
Okay.
The Rightflank Fortress
But it happened half a month ago.
It was 17 days ago to be exact.
Yes, the first time in a month and a half since Bepo and the others arrived,
the visitor's bell rang all over the Mokomo Dukedom.
But...
That was...
...the seldom-heard Raiding Bell!
What's that bell?
That's the Raiding Bell!
What?!
Raiding?!
No wonder a young lady like you-gara doesn't know.
It rarely rings.
The gate has been broken down! It's pirates!
Cutting up the forest along the way,
the enemy invaded our peaceful city.
Feeling such unusual movement,
Zunesha roared!
Who were they?! What did they want?!
If our vicious enemies want something that we don't have...
How can we give it to them?
Alright, give him to us now!
I know you have a warrior from the
Land of Wano named Raizou here!